Guide to the American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), District Council 1707 Records WAG.298
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series VIII: Unprocessed Material, 1972-2011
  - Union Security - Beck: Memorandum Robert W. McEncroe DC1707 - Union Security Issues, November, 9 1990 - May 21, 1990; cuid7507 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Union Security - Beck, May 31, 1990 - August 3, 1994; cuid7508 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - DC 1707: Day Care/Child Abuse Guidelines, February 14, 1985; cuid7509 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - DC 1707: Day Care/Child Abuse Guidelines pt. II, February 14, 1985; cuid7510 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - DC 1707: Day Care/Child Abuse pt. I - Reports, December 11, 1984 - February 14, 1985; cuid7511 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - DC 1707: Day Care/Child Abuse pt. II - Guidelines, October 1972 - December 4, 1984; cuid7512 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - DC 1707: Day Care/Child Abuse pt. I - News Clippings, June 20, 1984 - November 16, 1990; cuid7513 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - DC 1707: Day Care/Child Abuse pt. II - Legal Research (Miscellaneous, Fingerprinting, Criminal Record Checks), September 7, 1984 - February 13, 1985; cuid7514 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - DC 1707: Day Care/Child Abuse pt. I - Reports, August 10, 1984 - May 1988; cuid7515 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - DC 1707: Day Care/Child Abuse pt. II - Local 205 Welfare & Legal Fund, June 1989; cuid7516 (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - DC 1707: Day Care/Child Abuse pt. III - Position Papers, October 4, 1984 - April 16, 1985; cuid7517 (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - DC 1707: Day Care/Child Abuse pt. I - Laws & Regulations, May 24, 1976 - September 13, 1984; cuid7518 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - DC 1707: Day Care/Child Abuse pt. II - Legislative History, 1978 - November 7, 1985; cuid7519 (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - DC 1707: Day Care/Child Abuse pt. I - General Correspondence, August 5, 1982 - March 1, 1990; cuid7520 (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - DC 1707: Day Care/Child Abuse pt. II - Correspondence from City, August 15, 1984 - August 1, 1988; cuid7521 (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - DC 1707: LM #1 pt. I - DC 1707 and Ernesto Ramos Antonini Day Care Center - Bienvenido A. Taveras, February 17, 1982 - April 3, 1984; cuid7522 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - DC 1707: LM #1 pt. II - Arb. Award, NLRB Charge, Memo against Agency for Child Development, NLRB Charge, Arb. Award, July 1, 1981 - April 24, 1984; cuid7523 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - DC 1707: LM #1 pt. III - CSAEU, Settlement Agreement, 1983-1987; cuid7524 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - DC 1707: LM #2 pt. I, November 30, 1980 - March 1987; cuid7525 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - DC 1707: LM #2 pt. II, November 30, 1983 - November 29, 1988; cuid7526 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - DC 1707: LM #2 pt. III, May 6, 1982 - December 21, 1987; cuid7527 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - DC 1707: LM #2 pt. IV, May 6, 1982 - March 30, 1987; cuid7528 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - DC 1707: LM #3 pt. I - Rosa Gilyard v. Bronxdale Tenants League Day Care Center Union, Position Statement, Arb. Award, DC 1707 & Hadssah, The Woman's Zionist Org. of America, Napolean Holmes against New Rochelle Community Action Agency, April 1, 1981 - May 27, 1988; cuid7529 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - DC 1707: LM #3 pt. II - Petition, Arb. Award, Hamilton Madison Headstart, Proper Pay rate for Hattie White, Arb. Award, Jewish Assoc. for Services for the aged, December 27, 1982 - June 1, 1987; cuid7530 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - DC 1707: LM #3 pt. III - Letter Brief, Overtime for Merrileee Possner, Arb Award Stuyvesant Residence Club, Arb. Award Ruth Bronznick, James A. Krauskopf, Order Pursuant to Article 75, AA: "The Ladies" committee for Puerto Rican Culture Incorp. Dr. Ramon Betances Day Care, March 17, 1981 - September 14, 1988; cuid7531 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - DC 1707: LM #4 pt. I - YWCA & YMCA CAY CARE, Arb. Award New Mvmt Daycare, DC 1707 CSAEU & NAACP, Valarie Graham, Interim Award Ntl Board of the Young Women's Christian Assoc., Ronald v. Neal v. Institute of Int'l Edu and W. B. Edgerton, August 9, 1982 - April 29, 1985; cuid7532 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - DC 1707: LM #4 pt. II - Arb. Award NAACP, Termination of Barbara Wilkins and Dorothea Ryans, Decision & Award NAACP, Arb. Opinion/Award, Brief - DC 1707 v. NAACP East NY Day Care Center, Arb. Award Re: L. 205 and NAACP East NY Day Care, Award of Staff Arbitrator, Supplemental Award of Arb., August 31, 1978 - March 23, 1983; cuid7533 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - DC 1707: LM #4 pt. III - Ruth Orenstein, Order - Ronald v. Neal v. Inst. Intl. Edu., Bettye Roberts v. Police Athletic League, Arb. Award Vacation to earned employees, Termination of Tommie Thorpe, Allen Green and Park Place Day Care Center, Memo of Law, Arb opinion/award, 1981-1984; cuid7534 (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - DC 1707: LM #5 pt. I - Arb. Award, Arb. Award, Dismiss in the Interest, NLRB, Arb. Award, Arb. Award, NLRB Salvation Army, NY Supreme Court - Bettye W. Roberts, Arb. Award, Termination of Monseratte Irizzary, Together We Stand Women's Guild Day Care Center, 1981-1993; cuid7535 (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - DC 1707: LM #5 pt. II - Memo. Jewish Board of Family and Children's Services, Application of YWCA & YMCA, 1982-1988; cuid7536 (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - DC 1707: LM #7 pt. I - Employer Med. Plan improvement, Long Island Day Care Services, DCI, Sheltering Arms, Arb. Award, Arb. Award, Chama Child Development Center, Mary Obago, Louise Wise services, Letter Brief re Paul Parker, 1984-1989; cuid7537 (Box 49, Folder 16)
  - DC 1707: LM #7 pt. II - Members at UJA Federation, DCI re Carole Yudain, Quincy Lexinton Day Care Center, Vincent Bostic, American Jewish Committee, Arb. Award, 1976-1989; cuid7538 (Box 49, Folder 17)
  - Bostic v. DC 1707 pt. I, 1986-1987; cuid7539 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Bostic v. DC 1707 pt. II, 1987; cuid7540 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Yvette Titus v. DC 1707 & JBFCS: Duty of Fair Representation pt. I, 1986-1987; cuid7541 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Yvette Titus v. DC 1707 & JBFCS: Duty of Fair Representation pt. II, 1987-1988; cuid7542 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - DC 1707: Day Care/Child Abuse - Arbitration pt. I - Research, 1984; cuid7543 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - DC 1707: Day Care/Child Abuse - Arbitration pt. II - Cases, 1978-1986; cuid7544 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - DC 1707: LM #8 pt. I - NLRB Decision, Bramble v. AFSCME, NLRB Charge AFSCME, Arb. Award, Development Corp. for Israel, Dettye Roberts, Educational Alliance, Emanuel- Midtown Jewish Community Center, Consent Award: Jamaica Day Nursery, Jewish Assoc. for services to aged, Jewish Board of Family & Children's Services, 1978-1990; cuid7545 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - DC 1707: LM #8 pt. II - Mott Haven Day Care Center, Plaza Headstart, Arb. Award, PAL, Inc., Sheltering Arms Childrens Services, Arb. Award, Retirement Plan, Arb. Award, Zionist Org of America, 1982-1990; cuid7546 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Lenora Mack v. Bellevue, DC 37 Local 420 & Mary Obago v. UAHC, DC 1707, 1989-1990; cuid7547 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - L. 215, DC 1707 & International Rescue Committee - Transcripts, June - July 2005; cuid7548 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - International Rescue Committee & DC 1707 pt. I - Case Materials, May - September 2005; cuid7549 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - L. 215 & International Rescue Committee Decertification Petition & ULP, 2000-2005; cuid7550 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Employee Benefits Conference, 2010-2011; cuid7551 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - DC 1707 Videos on 1199 National benefit, Social Security, Southern Poverty Law Center, AFSCME, and Long-term Care Crisis, 1988-1996; cuid7553 (Box Shared Tamiment 012, Cassette 1-5)
  - Film cartridge: "AFSCME Retirees: Fighting for Dignity and Sceurity", undated; cuid7554 (Box Shared Tamiment 012, Cassette 6)
  - Film: "To Dream." property of 1707 CBTU Committee, undated; cuid7555 (Reel 1)
    Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
    16mm film
- Series IX: Archived Website, Nov 28, 2012-ongoing; cuid7552
  District Council 1707 of the American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees (AFSCME) is the only council within AFSCME that is chartered exclusively to represent private, nonprofit employees. It currently represents about 25,000 workers throughout the New York City area (and New York State), including those within private sector fundraising and advocacy agencies, case work and group work agencies, teaching and related organizations, child care centers, home care services, and Head Start programs. The website contains information on the political action committee, class and workshops, benefits, and news.
  Due to technical or privacy issues, archived websites may not be exact copies of the original website at the time of the web crawl. Certain file types will not be captured dependent on how they are embedded in the site. Other parts of websites that the crawler has difficulty capturing includes Javascript, streaming content, database-driven content, and highly interactive content. Full-Text searches of archived websites are available at https://archive-it.org/organizations/567.